absolutepoker.com 2009-11-30

# Support - Privacy

Last update: Friday, February 27th, 2009

Absolute Poker and this website is solely owned and operated by Tokwiro Enterprises ENRG, Route 138, Kahnawake, Quebec J0L 1B0. Tokwiro Enterprises ENRG is owned by a Mohawk of Kahnawake, and is operated from the sovereign nation of the Mohawks of Kahnawake, located near Montreal Quebec. The Mohawks of Kahnawake have an aboriginal right to conduct online gaming that is recognized and protected by the Canadian Constitution.

Absolute Poker is licensed by the [Kahnawake Gaming Commission](http://www.kahnawake.com/gamingcommission/) that enforces regulations designed to ensure, amongst other goals, that: (1) only suitable persons/entities operate within Kahnawake; (2) all games offered are fair to the player; and (3) all winners are paid.

Absolute Poker is vehemently committed to offering the highest-quality online poker experience combined with the highest level of integrity in dealing with our players. This policy was created to help you understand how we collect, use, and protect the personal information that you provide us. This is also to guide you in making informed decisions when using our products and services. We will frequently refer to and assess this agreement to take into consideration new technologies, business practices and your needs as a player at Absolute Poker.

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. If you would like more information about this practice and your choices, click here.

##### What Information Do We Collect?

Upon visiting our website, you may provide us with three different types of information: Personal information that you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis, website information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our website, and email information that may be kept in order to better facilitate communications with you and to keep records of inquiries that you may have.

__
  * Personal Information

If you choose to download Absolute Poker and register and account, you may need to provide the following information:

__
    * Name
__
    * Mailing Address
__
    * Email Address
__
    * Telephone Number
__
    * Other Information to help identify how you came across Absolute Poker
__
  * Email Information

If you choose to communicate with us using email, we may keep the content of your email messages associated with your email address and our responses to your inquiries. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.

__
  * Website Information

We use your Internet Protocol (IP) address to help diagnose potential problems with our servers and games, as well as to help administer our website. Your IP address can be used to help identify you, to track your activity within our servers and to gather broad demographic information. IP addresses may also be used to prevent fraud and collusion. 

##### How Do We Use Information That We Collect?

We use all information in order to provide quality customer service and to administer our business activities. Occasionally, we may also use the information collected to notify you about important changes to our website, new services, and special offers that we think you'll be glad to hear about. Your personal information may also be shared with our affiliates, subsidiaries, or agents for technical support and to process transactions you initiate and to deliver the products and services that you purchase. As a player at Absolute Poker, you will always be given the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by clicking on an unsubscribe link when you receive such an offer.

##### How Do We Secure Information Transmissions?

All of the communications between the Absolute Poker servers in Canada and the client program running on your computer are encrypted using the internationally accepted industry standard SSLv3/TLSv1 encryption algorithm. This means that your personal information, your account information, and any transaction information is protected using the same level of security that a bank would use. Our corporate values, ethical standards, policies and practices are committed to the protection of customer information. Our business practices limit employee access to confidential information, and limit the use and disclosure of such information to authorized persons, processes and transactions.

##### Changes to This Agreement

Changes to this Privacy Agreement may be deemed necessary by Absolute Poker and will be made occasionally. In such event, Absolute Poker will update this web page as published here within reasonable time.
